[
    {
        "questionText": "What is the name of the illustrious italian manufacturer of luxury sports cars?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "automobili lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "suvs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "groundbreaking innovations"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "a",
        "answer": "automobili lamborghini"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Lamborghini manufactures luxury sports cars and what else?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "Bikes"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "Big rigs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "suvs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "Hatchbacks"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "c",
        "answer": "suvs"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is the illustrious italian manufacturer of luxury sports cars and suvs?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "Lexus"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "Bmw"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "Maserati"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "c",
        "answer": "lamborghini"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What has led to the evolution of Lamborghini?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "groundbreaking innovations"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "suvs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "groundbreaking innovations"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "a",
        "answer": "groundbreaking innovations"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is the illustrious italian manufacturer of luxury sports cars and suvs?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "automobili lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "suvs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "ferruccio lamborghini"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "d",
        "answer": "ferruccio lamborghini"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Along with ownership changes, innovations and groundbreaking innovations, what has influenced the evolution of Lamborghini?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "Downturns"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "economic downturns"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "Capital flight"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "Increased unemployment"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "b",
        "answer": "economic downturns"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What type of performance is lamborghini known for?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "automobili lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "suvs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "formidable performance"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "groundbreaking innovations"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "c",
        "answer": "formidable performance"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What were lamborghini's first models called?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "automobili lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "inaugural models"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "groundbreaking innovations"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "b",
        "answer": "inaugural models"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is the style of Lamborghini?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "automobili lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "suvs"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "lamborghini"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "audacious"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "d",
        "answer": "audacious"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What type of investment did mycom setdco and indonesian group acquire Lamborghini?",
        "options": [
            {
                "optionId": "a",
                "optionValue": "Ministry"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "b",
                "optionValue": "Expert advice"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "c",
                "optionValue": "guidance"
            },
            {
                "optionId": "d",
                "optionValue": "Understanding"
            }
        ],
        "correctOption": "c",
        "answer": "guidance"
    }
]